Sit, stay, save the world.
DC League of Super-Pets is a family, comedy,
adventure film directed by Jared Stern.
When Superman and the rest of the Justice League are kidnapped, Krypto the Super-Dog must convince a rag-tag shelter pack - Ace the hound, PB the
potbellied pig, Merton the turtle and Chip the squirrel - to master their own newfound powers and help him rescue the superheroes.
Krypto the Superdog / Anubis / Black Adam (voice), played by Dwayne Johnson.
Ace the Bat-Hound (voice), played by Kevin Hart.
Clark Kent / Superman (voice), played by John Krasinski.
Bruce Wayne / Batman (voice), played by Keanu Reeves.
Lulu (voice), played by Kate McKinnon.
PB (voice), played by Vanessa Bayer.
DC League of Super-Pets is a 2022 American animated
superhero film based on DC Comics characters.
It was directed by Jared Stern, who co-wrote it with John Whittington.
Dwayne Johnson stars as the voice of Krypto, alongside a supporting ensemble voice cast that includes Kevin Hart, Kate McKinnon, John
Krasinski, Vanessa Bayer, Natasha Lyonne, Diego Luna, Marc Maron, Thomas Middleditch, Ben Schwartz, and Keanu Reeves.
It tells the story of Superman's pet dog Krypto and shelter dog Ace who work with
other animals to save captured superheroes from Lex Luthor and Lulu.
During the early days of Warner Animation Group, Stern pitched the film in 2012, after working in an animal shelter, where he
noticed how older animals were less likely to be adopted and wondered about the idea of those pets having superpowers.
He was hired to write and direct a film about DC's
Legion of Super-Pets in July 2018.
Levine and Patricia Hicks joined the project in January 2019
as co-director and producer, respectively.
Johnson was signed on to voice Krypto in May 2021, while other main cast members were confirmed to join the voice
roles by June 2021, including Hart, McKinnon, Krasinski, Bayer, Lyonne, Luna, Maron, and Reeves.
The inspiration for the film's animation style came from
Art Deco architecture and illustrator J.C.
Leyendecker.
The animation was provided by Animal Logic.
DC League of Super-Pets premiered at the AMC The Grove in Los Angeles, California
on July 13, 2022, and was released in the United States on July 29.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and grossed
over $207 million worldwide on a $90 million budget.
DC League of Super-Pets was the last film to be produced and released by Warner
Animation Group before the animation studio label folded into Warner Bros.
Pictures Animation in 2023.
The film explores themes of superhero, villain,
based on comic, dog, super power.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.